<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Catbook</string>
    <!-- Storage for user name entered -->
    <string name="key_name">name</string>
    <string name="catbook_title">catbook</string>
    <string name="enter_your_name">Enter your name</string>
    <string name="start_button_text">Start your story</string>
    <string name="story_image_content_description">Story page image</string>
    <string name="next_chapter">Next chapter</string>
    <string name="enter_your_guess">Enter your guess</string>
    <string name="enter_guess">Enter guess</string>

    <!-- Chapter 1: The wake-up call -->
    <!-- Page 0 intro text -->
    <string name="page0">It\'s morning. You wake up and stretch your skinny paws. Your pretty fur is a bit fuzzy from sleeping, so you wash it until it looks fabulous again. It is almost dawn and your human is still asleep… When will he learn…?\n\nTrain your human to wake up when it\'\s time for breakfast, not when the black box next to his nest starts beeping.\n\nBelow are several training methods. Some methods are more effective than others and you may have to repeat them. But watch out not to push it too hard or the human might throw you out of the room and you will have to wait another century before he comes down for breakfast. Try a method and see how the human reacts to it.</string>
    <!-- Action text after clicking buttons -->
    <string name="page0_25points">The human stirs and turns on his other side. Keep going.</string>
    <string name="page0_50points">The human mumbles something to you, but is not getting out of his nest yet. Try again, but watch out not to annoy him.</string>
    <string name="page0_75points">The human sighs. Just one more little push.</string>
    <string name="page0_100points">The human submits. Somewhat slow he walks down with you to the kitchen.</string>
    <string name="page0_over_100points">You pushed it too hard. The human gets out of his nest, picks you up and throws you out of the room. Now you\'ll have to wait until he gets out on his own time.</string>
    <!-- Button text page 0 -->
    <string name="page0_choice1">Sit on the human\'s face</string>
    <string name="page0_choice2">\'Boop\' his nose</string>
    <string name="page0_choice3">Meow loud and non-stop</string>
    <string name="page0_choice4">Put on your cute face and purr</string>

    <!-- Chapter 2: Friend or Foe -->
    <!-- Page 1 intro text (JS 2a: user wins in chapter 1) -->
    <string name="page1">The human gives you your breakfast. As you eat, you see him mindlessly staring in front of him for a few seconds before he walks away and goes about his business.\n\nAfter breakfast you decide to go for a morning walk, using the little cat door. You convinced the human to install it a week ago by scratching the human door multiple times. Humans are slow learners. He\'s lucky to have you.\n\nAs you walk around in your kingdom you enjoy the smell of the spring flowers and the sounds of food flying around. Suddenly you see another cat. You don\'t know this one and he\'s in your territory. What do you do?</string>
    <!-- Page 2 intro text (JS 2b: user loses in chapter 1) -->
    <string name="page2">After what seems like ages the human finally comes out of his room. You meow as loud as you can at him and he follows you to the kitchen where he gives you your food.\n\nAfter breakfast you decide to go for a morning walk, using the little cat door. You convinced the human to install it a week ago by scratching the human door multiple times. Humans are slow learners. He\'s lucky to have you.\n\nAs you walk around in your kingdom you enjoy the smell of the spring flowers and the sounds of food flying around. Suddenly you see another cat. You don\'t know this one and he\'s in your territory. What do you do?</string>
    <!-- After page1_choice1 -->
    <string name="page1_1">You sit down and blink to the cat as a sign of kindness. The cat blinks back to you and slowly walks your way. The two of you sniff each other. \"My name is Snuggles\", says the cat.\nYou: \"My name is %1$s.\"\nSnuggles: \"Nice to meet you, %1$s! I just moved here with my humans. I don\'t know this place very well yet. Could you show me around?\"</string>
    <!-- After page1_choice2 -->
    <string name="page1_2">You curl your back and hiss. The strange cat looks at you and… blinks. He walks towards you a few steps and lets himself fall to the ground. He keeps blinking and says: \"Hello, I\'m Snuggles. Who are you?\"</string>
    <!-- After page1_choice1_1 -->
    <string name="page1_3">You: \"Alright, Snuggles. Follow me and feast your eyes!\"</string>
    <!-- After page1_choice2_1 -->
    <string name="page1_4">Snuggles: \"Alright, see you later then!\"\nYou: \"Goodbye, Snuggles!\"\n\nYou\'re happy you made a new friend. It\'s good to have allies.</string>
    <!-- After page1_choice1_2 -->
    <string name="page1_5">You: \"Hello Snuggles, my name is %1$s\"\nSnuggles: \"Nice to meet you, %1$s! I just moved here with my humans.\"\nYou: \"Nice to meet you too. I\'m sorry for starting off like that.\"\nSnuggles: \"I understand. Some cats these days, right…\"\nYou: \"Totally…\"\nSnuggles: \"I don\'t know this place very well yet. Could you show me around?\"</string>
    <!-- After page1_choice2_2 -->
    <string name="page1_6">You run towards Snuggles and scratch him on his nose. Snuggles jumps up and hisses at you. \n\"Are you mad?!\" he meows, and as he runs away he yells: \"You will regret this!\"</string>
    <!-- Button text page 1 and 2 -->
    <string name="page1_choice1">Try to befriend him</string>
    <string name="page1_choice2">He\'s an intruder in your kingdom! Chase him away!</string>
    <!-- After page1_choice1 -->
    <string name="page1_choice1_1">Sure, follow me</string>
    <string name="page1_choice2_1">No, maybe some other time</string>
    <!-- After page1_choice2 -->
    <string name="page1_choice1_2">You calm down. Maybe he\'s not so bad. You tell him your name.</string>
    <string name="page1_choice2_2">It\'s a trap! You keep hissing and then attack him.</string>

    <!-- Chapter 3: Everything the light touches -->
    <!-- Page 3 intro text (JS 3a: user shows Snuggles kingdom) -->
    <string name="page3">You take Snuggles with you for a walk through your kingdom. You both climb up a fence so you can see the surroundings.\n\nYou: \"Look Snuggles, everything the light touches is my kingdom.\"\nSnuggles: \"Wow!\"\nYou: \"Behind us is the park, where you can find all sorts of snacks and toys to play with. In front of us you can see my house at the corner. Where is yours?\"\nSnuggles: \"It\'s just opposite your house! Wait, what about that shadowy place over there?\"\nYou: \"That\'s beyond my borders. You must never go there, Snuggles!\"\nSnuggles: \"Why?\"\nYou: \"Something evil lurks there in the dark. My nemesis. His name is \'Lucky\'. Don\'t be fooled by the name though. If he catches you, you\'re dog food.\"\nSnuggles: \"Noted, I\'ll stay away from that place.\"\nYou: \"Good.\"\nSnuggles: \"Would you like to see my house? I\'ll introduce you to my humans.\"</string>
    <!-- After page3_choice1 -->
    <string name="page3_1">Snuggles leads you to his place. Through the backyard you reach the door. Snuggles also has a cat door. Snuggles goes in first. You stick your head through the door and look around.\nSnuggles: \"It\'s alright, come in\"\nYou get in. You\'re in the kitchen where Snuggles has his water and food. There\'s a little left.\nSnuggles: \"You can eat that if you want. It\'s fish!\"</string>
    <!-- After page3_choice2 -->
    <string name="page3_2">Snuggles: \"Alright, see you later then!\"\nYou: \"Goodbye, Snuggles!\"\n\nYou\'re happy you made a new friend. It\'s good to have allies.</string>
    <!-- After choice1_1 -->
    <string name="page3_3">You eat the food. It\'s delicious! You have to convince your human to get this for you as well. Suddenly one of Snuggles\' humans walks into the kitchen and sees you eat. It\'s a female. She calls out something and the male human walks in. He yells: \"Snuggles!\"\n\nThe male walks towards you and waves his hands, forcing you to the door.\nSnuggles: \"I\'m sorry, I don\'t think he likes you very much. You should probably go. I\'ll talk to my humans.\"\nYou nod and run back outside. As you look back you see the male looking at you through the window before turning away. Humans are weird! But you\'ll be back and they will learn to love you!</string>
    <!-- After choice2_1 -->
    <string name="page3_4">Snuggles: \"Alright. Come, let\'s find my humans.\"\nAs you walk through the house you see a lot of boxes. Heaven! Then you see them. They are a male and a female human and they are taking things out of the boxes and putting it at random places in the room.\nSnuggles: \"Humans! Look, I brought my new friend!\"\nMale human: \"Ah, Snuggles!\"\nThe female says something to him in human speak and then walks over to you saying words in a soft voice. You only understand the word \'cute\'. She pets you and you purr in response. The male doesn\'t seem to like you very much, but submits to the female\'s command.\nThe female picks you up. You don\'t really like it when humans do that, but you let her. She walks you to the front door and puts you outside.\nSnuggles follows her: \"I\'m sorry for my male human, he doesn\'t seem to enjoy the company of other cats a lot.\"\nYou: \"That\'s ok, I like your female human.\"\nSnuggles: \"She likes you too! Listen, I think my humans need help with the boxes and all their stuff. So I\'ll see you around later.\"\nYou: \"Alright, see you Snuggles!\"</string>
    <!-- Button text page 3 -->
    <string name="page3_choice1">Sure, let\'s go</string>
    <string name="page3_choice2">No thank you, maybe some other time</string>
    <string name="page3_choice1_1">Eat the food</string>
    <string name="page3_choice2_1">No thanks, I\'ll pass</string>

    <!-- Chapter 3: The guessing game -->
    <!-- Page 4 intro text (JS 3b: user chases Snuggles away in Chapter 2, now plays the guessing game with Puddles) -->
    <string name="page4">You continue your walk through your kingdom. It\'s nice and sunny. As you sniff in the fresh air, you hear something move under a bush behind you. You slowly walk to the bush to check it out.\nSuddenly, someone jumps out and yells at you. You jump back and give a loud hiss. Then you see it\'s Puddles, the stray cat. He\'s your friend… but not very right in the head.\n\nYou: \"Oh… Hello, Puddles. You startled me! Don\'t do that again!\"\nPuddles: \"Sorry, bro! I thought you was a thief who was out for ma loot.\"\nYou: \"Your loot? What have you got there?\"\nYou try to see what\'s in the bushes behind Puddles.\nPuddles: \"No, you can\'t see it! It\'s mine!\"\nYou: \"Oh, come on! Don\'t be a kitten. Just let me see.\"\nPuddles: \"No!\"\n\nAs you try to move past Puddles he keeps blocking your way. You then take a few steps back and initiate a staring contest. Puddles tries, but within a minute he looks away.\nPuddles: \"Damn! OK, tell you what, bro: if you can guess what I got under this bush, you can see it. Deal?\"\n\nEnter whatever you think Puddles has hidden under the bush and hit the Enter button to guess. If you grow tired of Puddles\' guessing game, go to the next chapter.</string>
    <!-- Puddles' answers after guess -->
    <string name="key_guess">Guess</string>
    <string name="page4_1">Puddles: \"Yes!\"\nPuddles turns around and takes the %1$s out.\nPuddles: \"Guess again!\"</string>
    <string name="page4_2">Puddles: \"No! You guessed wrong! Try again!\"</string>
    <string name="page4_3">You already guessed that item. Try something else.</string>
    <string name="page4_4">Puddles: \"Yes!\"\nPuddles turns around and takes the %1$s out.\nPuddles: \"You guessed all my items! Sure you didn\'t peek?\"</string>

    <!-- Chapter 4: To catch a snack -->
    <!-- Page 5 intro text (JS 4a: after Chapter 3: showing Snuggles kingdom and going to his house) -->
    <string name="page5">Leaving Snuggles\' house behind, you make your way into the park across the road. This is the best place of your kingdom. It\'s filled with bushes to hide under, trees to climb in and there\'s snacks everywhere.\n\nYou think about what happened yesterday. Your girlfriend and you had a little fight. You should probably make things right with her. You know she loves a snack, but what will you catch her?\n\nShe likes birds best. Easy to find, but hard to catch.\nMice are her second-best favorite snack. They are hard to find at daylight and tricky to catch.\nButterflies are her third-best favorite. Not that hard to find and easier to catch than mice.\nSpiders are a little tricky to find, but a very easy catch. Spiders are also a nice snack, but girlfriend prefers the others. You think it\'s the web-like taste of them…\n\nAnyway, let\'s find her a nice snack! And be lucky to catch it!</string>
    <!-- Page 6 intro text (JS 4c: after Chapter 3: Snuggles is enemy, or showed Snuggles kingdom, but not going to his house) -->
    <string name="page6">You sigh at Puddles. Both out of boredom and pity. You say goodbye and walk away. Now, back to the order of the day. Your girlfriend and you had a little fight the other day. You should probably make things right with her.\n\nYou make your way into the park across the road. This is the best place of your kingdom. It\'s filled with bushes to hide under, trees to climb in and snacks everywhere. You know your girlfriend loves a snack, but what will you catch her?\n\nShe likes birds best. Easy to find, but hard to catch.\nMice are her second-best favorite snack. They are hard to find at daylight and tricky to catch.\nButterflies are her third-best favorite. Not that hard to find and easier to catch than mice.\nSpiders are a little tricky to find, but a very easy catch. Spiders are also a nice snack, but girlfriend prefers the others. You think it\'s the web-like taste of them…\n\nAnyway, let\'s find her a nice snack! And be lucky to catch it!</string>
    <!-- Button text page 5, 6 -->
    <string name="page5_choice1">Catch snack</string>
    <string name="page5_choice2">Find snack</string>
    <!-- Found snack first attempt -->
    <string name="page5_find1_mouse">You found a mouse! They are very hard to find, so well done! Your girlfriend will like it! It\'s tricky to catch though. Will you catch this mouse or try to find another snack one more time?</string>
    <string name="page5_find1_spider">You found a spider! Tricky to find, but a very easy catch! Your girlfriend might not like a spider that much, but better something than nothing. Will you catch this spider or try to find another snack one more time?</string>
    <string name="page5_find1_butterfly">You found a butterfly! Not so hard to find and pretty easy to catch. You will have a good chance at making up with your girlfriend! Will you catch this butterfly or try to find another snack one more time?</string>
    <string name="page5_find1_bird">You found a bird! They are very easy to find, but very hard to catch! Birds are your girlfriend\'s favorite snacks. Will you catch this bird or try to find another snack one more time?</string>
    <!-- Found snack second attempt -->
    <string name="page5_find2_mouse">You found a mouse! They are very hard to find, so well done! Your girlfriend will like it! It\'s tricky to catch though. So focus!</string>
    <string name="page5_find2_spider">You found a spider! Tricky to find, but a very easy catch! Your girlfriend might not like a spider that much, but better something than nothing. Go catch it!</string>
    <string name="page5_find2_butterfly">You found a butterfly! Not so hard to find and pretty easy to catch. You will have a good chance at making up with your girlfriend! Catch it!</string>
    <string name="page5_find2_bird">You found a bird! They are very easy to find, but very hard to catch! Birds are your girlfriend\'s favorite snacks. Remember your mum\'s lessons: focus!</string>
    <!-- Caught snack first attempt : no catch -->
    <string name="page5_catch1_mouse">The mouse got away, but you see it trying to hide behind a stone a few metres away. Try one more time!</string>
    <string name="page5_catch1_spider">The spider got away, but crawls at high speed (for a spider) across the grass. Try one more time!</string>
    <string name="page5_catch1_butterfly">The butterfly got away, but lands on the flower a few metres away. Try one more time!</string>
    <string name="page5_catch1_bird">The bird got away, but lands on the grass a few metres away. Try one more time!</string>
    <!-- Caught snack attempt : catched it -->
    <string name="page5_catch2_mouse">You caught the mouse! Take it to your girlfriend.</string>
    <string name="page5_catch2_spider">You caught the spider! Take it to your girlfriend.</string>
    <string name="page5_catch2_butterfly">You caught the butterfly! Take it to your girlfriend.</string>
    <string name="page5_catch2_bird">You caught the bird! Take it to your girlfriend.</string>
    <!-- Caught snack second attempt : no catch (fail) -->
    <string name="page5_catch3_mouse">You didn\'t catch the mouse. There is no time to find another snack. Hopefully your girlfriend will forgive you without one.</string>
    <string name="page5_catch3_spider">You didn\'t catch the spider. There is no time to find another snack. Hopefully your girlfriend will forgive you without one.</string>
    <string name="page5_catch3_butterfly">You didn\'t catch the butterfly. There is no time to find another snack. Hopefully your girlfriend will forgive you without one.</string>
    <string name="page5_catch3_bird">You didn\'t catch the bird. There is no time to find another snack. Hopefully your girlfriend will forgive you without one.</string>
    <!-- Take snack to Leia -->
    <string name="page5_mouse">You take the mouse to your girlfriend\'s home. But along the route you feel as if someone is following and watching you. You look behind you a couple of times, but there\'s no one there. Must still be the excitement of the hunt…\n\nYou jump on the fence surrounding your girlfriend\'s garden and look for her. There she is! Sitting in the sun washing her beautiful white fur. Alright now, be on your best! You jump down into the garden and walk to her.\n\nYou place the dead mouse in front of her, sit down, purr and say: \"I\'m sorry, Leia! Can you forgive me? Here, I brought you this dead mouse.\"\nLeia remains silent for a moment, still looking angry. She then looks at the mouse and back at you again. \"You catch this yourself?\" She asks.\n\"Uhu, uhu!\" You say proud.\nLeia: \"Thank you. That\'s very nice of you. I like mice.\"\nYou: \"I know! And I\'m really sorry, and you\'re the most beautiful kitty in the kingdom.\"\nLeia: \"Hmm… Just don\'t EVER push me into the pond again.\"\nYou lower your head: \"Yeah… I don\'t know what got into me. I just felt the random need all of a sudden to run around your garden like crazy and didn\'t notice you sitting next to the pond.\"\nLeia gives you a headbutt and a lick on your nose. \"It\'s OK.\"\n\nLeia eats her mouse and leaves some for you. Then you wash your furs and together you take a nap under a bush.</string>
    <string name="page5_spider">You take the spider to your girlfriend\'s home. But along the route you feel as if someone is following and watching you. You look behind you a couple of times, but there\'s no one there. Must still be the excitement of the hunt…\n\nYou jump on the fence surrounding your girlfriend\'s garden and look for her. There she is! Sitting in the sun washing her beautiful white fur. Alright now, be on your best! You jump down into the garden and walk to her.\n\nYou place the dead spider in front of her, sit down, purr and say: \"I\'m sorry, Leia! Can you forgive me? Here, I brought you this spider.\"\nLeia remains silent for a moment, still looking angry. She then looks at the spider and back at you again. \"A spider? Is that the best you can do for what you did yesterday?\" She asks.\nYou: \"I didn\'t find anything else. But I\'m really sorry!\"\nLeia: \"You pushed me into the pond! It took me hours to wash up!\"\nYou lower your head: \"Yeah… I don\'t know what got into me. I just felt the random need all of a sudden to run around your garden like crazy and didn\'t notice you sitting next to the pond.\"\nLeia sighs: \"I don\'t know… I\'ll think about this.\"\n\nLeia picks up the spider and takes it inside her house. You sigh, hoping she will like the spider and forgive you.</string>
    <string name="page5_butterfly">You take the butterfly to your girlfriend\'s home. But along the route you feel as if someone is following and watching you. You look behind you a couple of times, but there\'s no one there. Must still be the excitement of the hunt…\n\nYou jump on the fence surrounding your girlfriend\'s garden and look for her. There she is! Sitting in the sun washing her beautiful white fur. Alright now, be on your best! You jump down into the garden and walk to her.\n\nYou place the dead butterfly in front of her, sit down, purr and say: \"I\'m sorry, Leia! Can you forgive me? Here, I brought you this butterfly.\"\nLeia remains silent for a moment, still looking angry. She then looks at the butterfly and back at you again. \"A butterfly? Is that the best you can do for what you did yesterday?\" She asks.\nYou: \"I didn\'t find anything else. But I\'m really sorry!\"\nLeia: \"You pushed me into the pond! It took me hours to wash up!\"\nYou lower your head: \"Yeah… I don\'t know what got into me. I just felt the random need all of a sudden to run around your garden like crazy and didn\'t notice you sitting next to the pond.\"\nLeia sighs: \"I guess I\'ll forgive you.\"\n\nLeia eats her butterfly. After she is finished, you wash her fur and together you take a nap under a bush.</string>
    <string name="page5_bird">You take the bird to your girlfriend\'s home. But along the route you feel as if someone is following and watching you. You look behind you a couple of times, but there\'s no one there. Must still be the excitement of the hunt…\n\nYou jump on the fence surrounding your girlfriend\'s garden and look for her. There she is! Sitting in the sun washing her beautiful white fur. Alright now, be on your best! You jump down into the garden and walk to her.\n\nYou place the dead bird in front of her, sit down, purr and say: \"I\'m sorry, Leia! Can you forgive me? Here, I brought you this dead bird.\"\nLeia remains silent for a moment, still looking angry. She then looks at the bird and back at you again. \"You catch this yourself?\" She asks.\n\"Uhu, uhu!\" You say proud.\nLeia: \"Thank you. That\'s very nice of you. Birds are my favorite.\"\nYou: \"I know! And I\'m really sorry, and you\'re the most beautiful kitty in the kingdom.\"\nLeia: \"Hmm… Just don\'t EVER push me into the pond again.\"\nYou lower your head: \"Yeah… I don\'t know what got into me. I just felt the random need all of a sudden to run around your garden like crazy and didn\'t notice you sitting next to the pond.\"\nLeia gives you a headbutt and a lick on your nose. \"It\'s OK.\"\n\nLeia eats her bird and leaves some for you. Then you wash your furs and together you take a nap under a bush.</string>
    <string name="page5_nothing">Failing to catch a snack, you walk to your girlfriend\'s home. Along the route you feel as if someone is following and watching you. You look behind you a couple of times, but there\'s no one there. Must still be the excitement of the hunt…\n\nYou jump on the fence surrounding your girlfriend\'s garden and look for her. There she is! Sitting in the sun washing her beautiful white fur. Alright now, be on your best! You jump down into the garden and walk to her.\n\nYou sit down, purr as loud as you can and say: \"I\'m really sorry, Leia! Can you forgive me?\"\nLeia remains silent, looking angry.\nYou: \"I… I don\'t know what got into me yesterday. I just felt the random need all of a sudden to run around your garden like crazy and didn\'t notice you sitting next to the…\"\nLeia: \"YOU PUSHED ME INTO THE POND! It took me hours to wash up!\"\nYou lower your head: \"Please Leia, I\'m really sorry…\"\nLeia sighs: \"I don\'t know… I have to think about this.\"\n\nLeia turns around and walks into her house. You sigh, hoping she will eventually forgive you.</string>
    <!-- Button text take snack to girlfriend -->
    <string name="take_snack_to_gf">Take snack to girlfriend</string>

    <!-- Chapter 5: The human and the light box -->   <!-- Skipping page 7, was broken -->
    <!-- Page 8 intro text (JS 5b: Snuggles = friend, Leia = angry) -->
    <string name="page8">You wake up from your nap. As you wash your fur you think back about your day. Leia is still angry and that bothers you. But at least you made a new friend. You decide to check on your human. Maybe he can distract you from your thoughts of Leia.\n\nYou walk inside your house and see your human sitting in his chair at the desk, pressing his fingers on buttons and staring at the light-box in front of him. Poor human… He doesn\'t understand that nothing is going to come out of that box and that everything he needs is right here: you! It\'s your duty as his cat to get him away from the light-box. How will you do this?</string>
    <!-- Page 9 intro text (5c: Snuggles = enemy, Leia = happy) -->
    <string name="page9">After your nap with Leia you give her a last lick before walking back home. It\'s been a busy day. You had to chase away that intruder, Snuggles. You spy your surroundings as you walk, but he is nowhere in sight. You\'re happy you made up with your girlfriend. You can\'t stand it when she\'s mad. You decide to check on your human.\n\nYou walk inside your house and see your human sitting in his chair at the desk, pressing his fingers on buttons and staring at the light-box in front of him. Poor human… He doesn\'t understand that nothing is going to come out of that box and that everything he needs is right here: you! It\'s your duty as his cat to get him away from the light-box. How will you do this?</string>
    <!-- Page 10 intro text (JS 5d: Snuggles = enemy, Leia = angry) -->
    <string name="page10">You wake up from your nap. As you wash your fur you think back about your day, which hasn\'t been an very good one. Leia is still angry and that bothers you. You also had to chase away that intruder, Snuggles. You look out the window to see if he\'s there somewhere, but he\'s nowhere in sight. You decide to check on your human.\n\nYou walk inside your house and see your human sitting in his chair at the desk, pressing his fingers on buttons and staring at the light-box in front of him. Poor human… He doesn\'t understand that nothing is going to come out of that box and that everything he needs is right here: you! It\'s your duty as his cat to get him away from the light-box. How will you do this?</string>
    <!-- Page 11 intro text (JS 5a: Snuggles = friend, Leia = happy) -->
    <string name="page11">After your nap with Leia you give her a last lick before walking back home. It\'s been a good day so far. You made a new friend and you made up with your girlfriend. You decide to check on your human.\n\nYou walk inside your house and see your human sitting in his chair at the desk, pressing his fingers on buttons and staring at the light-box in front of him. Poor human… He doesn\'t understand that nothing is going to come out of that box and that everything he needs is right here: you! It\'s your duty as his cat to get him away from the light-box. How will you do this?</string>
    <!-- After page7_choice1_1 -->
    <string name="page7_1">You jump on the desk. You know the dust monster can\'t climb, so you\'re safe from it here.\n\nYou see the human show the monster every corner of the room. You have observed it many times and you concluded that it eats dust. So the human feeds it every now and then. You tried eating dust once, but it was no success… Actually it was gross. After the monster has fed enough, the human puts it back in the closet again where it lives. You climb down from the desk and walk to the closet. You don\'t see or hear it. It only comes out of its hibernation to eat. Not a bad way to live, you think.\n\nYour human goes back to his light-box and you decide to go back outside.</string>
    <!-- After page7_choice2_1 -->
    <string name="page7_2">As the human pushes the monster through the room, you attack it several times. But it keeps striking back! Your human seems to think it\'s funny… He doesn\'t understand the threat. You keep attacking it until the monster finally gives up and stops making the noise. The human puts it back in the closet. Well done! But keep an eye on that closet. You may have won this battle, but the war is far from over.\n\nNow that the human is safe again you decide to go back outside.</string>
    <!-- After page7_choice3_1 -->
    <string name="page7_3">Everything in the house is yours, and so is this box on wheels. You jump on it as the human pulls you forth. The human looks at you and laughs. He pulls out a smaller light-box from his pocket and points it at you. These light-boxes are like pests… They\'re everywhere.\n\nAs he keeps pulling the box forth he keeps pointing the light-box at you, while laughing. He then trips and falls over one of your toys, making the little light-box fly through the room. The human lies on his back and moans, so you comfort him by sitting on top of his chest purring.\n\nYou: \"It\'s OK, human. Just keep purring with me.\"\nHe pushes you off, stands back up and grabs the little light-box. Distracted again… You give up.\n\nYou decide to go outside.</string>
    <!-- Button text page 8, 9, 10, 11 -->
    <string name="page7_choice1">Sit on the keyboard</string>
    <string name="page7_choice2">Bring a toy to the desk</string>
    <string name="page7_choice3">Push a pen of the desk</string>
    <string name="page7_choice4">Meow and rub against his legs</string>
    <!-- Action text after clicking buttons -->
    <string name="page7_25points">The human gives you a pet, but then ignores you again. Maybe a harder push.</string>
    <string name="page7_50points">The human pushes you away. Try again, but watch out not to annoy him.</string>
    <string name="page7_75points">The human sighs and for a second he moves his eyes from the light-box to you. Just one more little push.</string>
    <string name="page7_100points">Finally! The human looks and smiles at you. He pets you and grabs a toy. You run to the table to hide under it. The human throws the toy and you catch it! It never gets old!\n\nThe human plays with you for a while and then looks back at his light-box again. He sighs and walks to the closet in the hall. He takes out the dust machine and turns it on. What do you do about it?</string>
    <string name="page7_over_100points">You pushed it too hard. The human sighs annoyed, picks you up and puts you in the hall, closing the door. Nothing to do now but take a nap until he comes to his senses.\n\nAfter a while the human opens the door again, but not to play with you. He opens the closet door and takes out the dust monster. He turns it on and starts pushing it through the living room. What do you do about it?</string>
    <!-- After getting human's attention -->
    <string name="page7_choice1_1">Jump to higher grounds where it\'s safe</string>
    <string name="page7_choice2_1">Attack the monster</string>
    <string name="page7_choice3_1">Sit on the box on wheels</string>

    <!-- Chapter 6: The game is on (with frog part) -->
    <!-- Page 12 intro text -->
    <string name="page12">You go back outside. There it is again, that funny feeling of someone watching you. You look around, but no one is there. You see Snuggles sitting in front of his house.\n\nYou: \"Hello Snuggles. Listen, have you seen anything strange today? Something feels odd…\"\nSnuggles: \"No, I haven\'t. It\'s very quiet though.\"\nYou: \"It is indeed…\"\nSnuggles: \"You just need some distraction. I talked to my humans this morning about that little argument. The male human is away now, but I think you have a chance winning the female over. She has a soft spot for cats. She also fears frogs more than anything, so I killed one that was lurking in the garden, ready to strike when she walked by. If you take it to her, you can pretend you killed it and saved her. What do you say?\"</string>
    <!-- After page12_choice1 -->
    <string name="page12_1">You pick up the dead frog and with your head up high you proudly present it right in front of the human her feet. She is so excited you killed it and saved her, she jumps up in the air and screams.\nSnuggles:\"Well done! I think she definitely likes you now! Look how excited she is!\"\nYou: \"Yes! Uhm, what is she doing now?\"\n\nYou see the female struggling to pick up the frog with a weird shovel like tool. It keeps falling off.\nYou: \"She knows she can just pick it up with her mouth, right? Or with her paws.\"\nSnuggles: \"Of course, we just showed her.\"\nYou watch the female struggle for a little longer, before she finally prevails with her method and throws the frog in the garbage bin outside.\n\nYou and Snuggles go outside, and you ask him: \"So what do we do now?\"\nSnuggles: \"Oh! I know! I know!\"He lifts his paw and boops you on the head. \"You\'re it!\" He runs away around the corner to hide.\nIt\'s on!</string>
    <!-- After page12_choice2 -->
    <string name="page12_2">You start eating the frog.\nSnuggles: \"Why are you eating it? Don\'t you want to surprise the human?\"\nYou: \"I don\'t think she really appreciates it when I do that, Snuggles.\"\nSnuggles: \"Sure she will! She always jumps up in excitement when I bring her a dead frog.\"\nYou: \"Oh, Snuggles…\" You throw him a piece of the dead frog. \"Just eat it.\"\nSnuggles looks at you a little confused, but then eats the frog.\nSnuggles: \"Hmm, good frog. Slimy, but satisfying.\"\nYou: \"Indeed. So now what do we do?\"\nSnuggles: \"Oh! I know! I know!\"He lifts his paw and boops you on the head. \"You\'re it!\" He runs away around the corner to hide.\nIt\'s on!</string>
    <!-- Page 12 without frog part (right into hide and seek) -->
    <string name="page13">You walk outside. There it is again, that funny feeling of someone watching you. You look around, but no one is there. You see Snuggles sitting in front of his house.\n\nYou: \"Hello Snuggles. Listen, have you seen anything strange today? Something feels odd.\"\nSnuggles: \"No, I haven\'t. It\'s very quiet though.\"\nYou: \"It is indeed…\"\nSnuggles: \"You just need some distraction.\"\n\nSnuggles jumps to you and boops you on your head. \"You\'re it!\" And he runs away around the corner to hide.\nIt\'s on!</string>
    <!-- Button text page 12 -->
    <string name="page12_choice1">Take the frog to the female human</string>
    <string name="page12_choice2">Eat the frog</string>
    <string name="page12_choice1_1">Play hide and seek</string>

    <!-- Chapter 6: The game is on (hide & seek part) -->
    <!-- Page 13 intro text -->
    <string name="page14">You run after Snuggles, but don\'t see him anywhere. He\'s hiding. Where are you going to look for him?</string>
    <!-- Answers while looking for Snuggles -->
    <string name="page14_1">He\'s not hiding behind the garbage bin. Choose another spot.</string>
    <string name="page14_2">Nice try, but he\'s not in the tree. Check another hiding spot.</string>
    <string name="page14_3">Bushes are good spots, yet no Snuggles here. Where else could he be?</string>
    <string name="page14_4">Not behind the car. Snuggles is hiding somewhere else.</string>
    <string name="page14_5">You found Snuggles! Now it\'s your turn. Choose a hiding spot.</string>
    <!-- After user chooses own hiding spot -->
    <string name="page14_6">You run around for a while and then hide %1$s. Snuggles lost you and looks for you. As he gets closer to your hiding spot, you get in your jumping position and wiggle your butt. Snuggles gets closer, and closer, and…\n\nYou: \"Gotcha!\" You jump out from your hiding spot, right on top of Snuggles.\nSnuggles: \"Oh! Nice hiding skills. You\'re like a ninja!\"\nYou: \"Thanks! I have to be, to protect my kingdom. Danger is everywhere!\"\n\nSuddenly you hear a lot of noise coming from the park. A dog barking and… is that Leia\'s cry?! You and Snuggles run towards the park to check it out.</string>
    <!-- Button text page 13 -->
    <string name="page14_choice1">Behind the garbage bin</string>
    <string name="page14_choice2">Up in the tree</string>
    <string name="page14_choice3">Under the bush</string>
    <string name="page14_choice4">Behind the car</string>

    <!-- Chapter 6: The investigation -->
    <string name="page15">You walk outside for your daily patrol through your kingdom. There it is again, that funny feeling of someone watching you. You look around, but no one is there.\n\nYou decide to visit some residents of your kingdom to see if they have seen anything strange going on. Get inquiries from:</string>
    <!-- Puddles the stray cat -->
    <string name="page15_1">You find Puddles at his usual spot on a patch of grass at the end of the street.\nYou: \"Hey, Puddles. What\'s up?\"\nPuddles: \"Hey, bro! Everything is cool! What\'s going on, yo?\"\nYou: \"I don\'t know. I have this weird feeling something is following me today. Have you seen anything strange?\"\nPuddles: \"Not really. Me and ma homies just chillin\' here.\"\nYou: \"Your… homies?\"\nPuddles: \"Yeah, bro! They in that hole over there! Big family of mice!\"\nYou: \"You have mouse friends now? Or are you pretending so you have an easy snack later?\"\nPuddles: \"Sssst! Don\'t tell them! They still don\'t see me as one of theirs yet.\"\nYou: \"No kidding.\"\nPuddles: \"No, man! I still have to earn their trust. But listen, if I see any weird things I will tell ya, alright?\"\nYou: \"…Sure. Good luck becoming a mouse, Puddles.\"\nPuddles: \"Thanks man!\"</string>
    <!-- Jon the crow -->
    <string name="page15_2">You figure that the best way to scan the area is to have eyes in the sky, so you pay a visit to your friend Jon the crow. He is sitting on a branch in his tree.\nYou: \"Hello Jon! How are the chicks?\"\nJon: \"Well, hello! My babies are fine, thank you! Ygritte is taking them out for a flying lesson, so I can rest for a bit. Parenting is hard sometimes.\"\nYou: \"I\'m sure. Listen Jon, something is not right today in the kingdom. Have you seen anything from the sky today?\"\nJon: \"Hmm, I haven\'t scanned the area properly today. Just a minute.\"\n\nJon takes off and flies around a couple of times, scanning with his crow eyes. You wish you could fly. Sometimes you do, but it feels more like falling than flying.\nAs Jon flies around you call: \"Jon! What do your crow eyes see?\"\nJon: \"Everything seems normal! Wait!\" He flies to a lower height through a few trees in the park. He then flies back and lands on the branch in his tree.\nYou: \"What was it?\"\nJon: \"I don\'t know. I thought I saw something move in the park under the trees, but there was nothing.\"\nYou: \"Odd…\"\nJon: \"If I do see something, I will let you know. I will ask Ygritte when she returns.\"\nYou: \"Thanks Jon. Have a nice day!\"\nJon: \"You too!\"</string>
    <!-- Rufus the dog -->
    <string name="page15_3">You see Rufus the Danish dog sitting in his garden, chest up and his nose in the air. He\'s on guard duty. As you walk over to him he starts barking: \"Who goes there!\"\nYou: \"Rufus, you know who I am…\"\nRufus: \"Yes, but how do I know it\'s really you? You could be another cat in disguise! Let me smell you from up close.\"\nYou: \"Do you really have to?\"\nRufus: \"Standard procedure, cat!\"\nYou: \"Ugh, fine.\" You get closer to Rufus and with his wet nose he almost sniffs the hairs out of your fur.\nRufus: \"ID has been verified! State your business, please.\"\nCovered in dog drool, you ask: \"Have you seen anything strange going on today? I feel like I\'m being followed.\"\nRufus\'s eyes narrow and alerted he turns his head left and right. He lowers his voice: \"I must say I have smelled something odd as well today. I couldn\'t place it. It\'s a smell I haven\'t smelled in a long time. You be careful, cat! Danger lurks everywhere!\"\nYou: \"Thanks Rufus. I\'ll be careful.\"\nRufus: \"You are dismissed then!\"\nYou flatten your ears at that comment. Without saying another word you turn around and walk away.</string>
    <!-- After all residents have been visited this string gets added to the last resident text -->
    <string name="page15_4">\n\nNone of the residents knew what was going on. You decide to look around yourself.\n\nSuddenly you hear a lot of noise coming from the park. A dog barking and… is that Leia\'s cry?! You run to the park to check it out.</string>
    <!-- Button text page 14 -->
    <string name="page15_choice1">Puddles the stray cat</string>
    <string name="page15_choice2">Jon the crow</string>
    <string name="page15_choice3">Rufus the dog</string>

    <!-- Chapter 7: Save the princess -->
    <!-- Page 16 intro text (Snuggles and user are friends and work together) -->
    <string name="page16">You and Snuggles run into the park and see Leia being cornered by Lucky the dog. You hiss at him to draw his attention. He notices you and gets ready to attack.\n\nYou have to save Leia.\nSnuggles jumps in beside you: \"Don\'t worry, pal! I\'ll help you!\"\n\nFight!</string>
    <!-- Damage string (formatted) -->
    <string name="page16_1">You and Snuggles attack!\nYou did %1$d damage!\nSnuggles did %2$d damage!\nLucky\'s health is down to %3$d.\n\nLucky attacks you and did %4$d damage!\nYour health is down to %5$d.</string>
    <!-- END: user wins, leia is happy and forgives -->
    <string name="page16_2">You give Lucky a last scratch on his nose before he finally gives up and runs away crying. Leia runs to you, hugs you and licks your face. \"Thank you! He almost had me!\"\nYou: \"I\'m glad you\'re OK. I was lucky I had Snuggles with me.\"\nLeia turns to your friend: \"Thank you too Snuggles. You were very brave!\"\nSnuggles: \"Ohw! It\'s nothing!\" If cats could blush, Snuggles would be as red as a beetroot.\n\nYou all walk home after a long day. Snuggles proved to be a fine soldier and friend. Leia is save and happy. And you saved the kingdom from evil Lucky once again.\n\nTHE END!</string>
    <!-- END: user wins, leia is angry and forgives -->
    <string name="page16_3">You give Lucky a last scratch on his nose before he finally gives up and runs away crying. Leia runs to you, hugs you and licks your face. \"Thank you! He almost had me!\"\nYou: \"I\'m glad you\'re OK. I was lucky I had Snuggles with me.\"\nLeia turns to your friend: \"Thank you too Snuggles. You were very brave!\"\nSnuggles: \"Ohw! It\'s nothing!\" If cats could blush, Snuggles would be as red as a beetroot.\nYou: \"Leia, can you forgive me now?\"\nLeia: \"Of course I forgive you, silly! You saved my life!\"\nYou smile.\n\nYou all walk home after a long day. Snuggles proved to be a fine soldier and friend. Leia is save and happy. And you saved the kingdom from evil Lucky once again.\n\nTHE END!</string>
    <!-- END: user loses, leia is happy and forgives -->
    <string name="page16_4">After a tiring fight, Lucky proves to outbest you this time. He wounded you and Snuggles too bad to continue. As he starts barking and attacking again, you are forced to run away and hide in a tree. Leia sees a chance to escape and runs away. Lucky runs after her. The kingdom has been taken over by Lucky the dog and Leia is probably not as happy with you anymore. You will have to fight for them both another day.\n\nTHE END!</string>
    <!-- END: user loses, leia is angry and doesn't forgive -->
    <string name="page16_5">After a tiring fight, Lucky proves to outbest you this time. He wounded you and Snuggles too bad to continue. As he starts barking and attacking again, you are forced to run away and hide in a tree. Leia sees a chance to escape and runs away. Lucky runs after her. The kingdom has been taken over by Lucky the dog and if Leia wasn\'t angry with you before, you probably will have to find yourself another princess now. You will have to fight for your kingdom another day.\n\nTHE END!</string>
    <!-- END: user ties, leia is happy and forgives -->
    <string name="page16_6">You and Lucky fight for what seems to be hours (or minutes). You both attempt a frontal attack and hit each other head to head.... and both faint.\n\nYou wake up after... minutes? Hours? Lucky is gone, but Leia and Snuggles are still there.\nLeia: \"Are you alright?\"\nYou: \"I don\'t know. Where is Lucky? Did we save the kingdom?\"\nSnuggles: \"I\'m not sure. Leia and I just waited and then Lucky woke up. We chased him away, he didn\'t seem to be in the mood for another fight.\"\nYou: \"So he could be anywhere. I have to find him...\"\nLeia: \"No, you\'re not! You have to go home and rest. You\'ll have to settle this another time.\"\n\nYou agree and together you walk home. Though the kingdom might not be save, at least Leia is happy you saved her and Snuggles proved to be a good friend.\n\nTHE END!</string>
    <!-- END: user ties, leia is angry and doesn't forgive -->
    <string name="page16_7">You and Lucky fight for what seems to be hours. You both attempt a frontal attack and hit each other head to head.... and both faint.\n\nYou wake up after... minutes? Hours? Lucky is gone, but Leia and Snuggles are still there.\nLeia: \"Are you alright?\"\nYou: \"I don\'t know. Where is Lucky? Did we save the kingdom?\"\nSnuggles: \"I\'m not sure. Leia and I just waited and then Lucky woke up. We chased him away, he didn\'t seem to be in the mood for another fight.\"\nYou: \"So he could be anywhere. I have to find him...\"\nLeia: \"No, you\'re not! You have to go home and rest. You\'ll have to settle this another time.\"\n\nYou agree and together you walk home. Though the kingdom might not be save, at least Snuggles proved to be a good friend. Leia is not very happy with you still. You will have to prove yourself again another day.\n\nTHE END!</string>
    <!-- Button text page 16 -->
    <string name="page16_choice1">Fight</string>
    <string name="page16_play_again">Play again</string>

    <!-- Page 17 intro text (Snuggles is enemy, user fights alone) -->
    <string name="page17">You run into the park and see Leia being cornered by Lucky the dog. You hiss at him to draw his attention. He notices you and gets ready to attack. You have to save Leia.\n\nYou see Snuggles lie down on top of the wall surrounding the park watching it happen. Coward!\n\nFight and save Leia!</string>
    <!-- Damage string (formatted) -->
    <string name="page17_1">You attack Lucky and did %1$d damage!\nLucky\'s health is down to %2$d.\n\nLucky attacks you and did %3$d damage!\nYour health is down to %4$d.</string>
    <!-- END: user wins, leia is happy and forgives -->
    <string name="page17_2">You give Lucky a last scratch on his nose before he finally gives up and runs away crying. Leia smiles and starts to run to you, but then Snuggles jumps between you two. He hisses at you and gets ready to attack.\nYou\'re too tired and injured from the fight with Lucky to win this one, you think. But then Leia attacks Snuggles from behind and bites him in his ear. Snuggles cries in pain and Leia holds on for as long as she can. After Snuggles frees himself from her grip he hisses at you both one more time before running of.\nYou: \"Thank you, Leia!\"\nLeia: \"I saw him watching and doing nothing all the time on top of the wall. He\'s a coward!\" She licks your face. \"But you are the true king! Thank you for saving my life.\"\nYou smile.\n\nYou both walk home after a long day. Leia is save and happy and you saved the kingdom from evil Lucky once again.\n\nTHE END!</string>
    <!-- END: user wins, leia is angry and forgives -->
    <string name="page17_3">You give Lucky a last scratch on his nose before he finally gives up and runs away crying. As you walk to Leia, suddenly Snuggles jumps between you two.\nSnuggles: \"Well, you really love a fight, do you, king?\"\nYou: \"Step aside, Snuggles!\"\nSnuggles turns around to Leia. \"Tell me, is he really the kind of cat you want to be with?\"\nLeia looks from Snuggles to you.\nYou: \"Leia, please don\'t go with him!\"\nSnuggles: \"Look at him! Kings don\'t beg! I\'ll be much stronger. Lucky won\'t even be able to leave his dark home.\"\nYou: \"Leia, I promise I will catch you a bird next time!\"\nSnuggles: \"One bird? I will catch you the entire flock!\"\nYou: \"Bugger off, Snuggles!\"\nSnuggles: \"What? You want to fight another round?!\"\nLeia: \"SHUT UP! BOTH OF YOU!\"\n\nYou both stop talking. Leia gets up and slowly walks towards you both. As she walks passed Snuggles she growls. She then walks to you, saying: \"Are you coming, my king?\"\nYou give Snuggles a last threatening look and then follow Leia.\nAs you walk out of the park you say: \"Thank you, Leia!\"\nLeia: \"I saw him watching and doing nothing all the time on top of the wall. He\'s a coward!\" She licks your face. \"You are the true king! Thank you for saving my life.\"\nYou smile.\nLeia: \"You owe me a bird, though.\"\nYou: \"No problem!\"\n\nYou both walk home after a long day. Leia is save and happy and you saved the kingdom from evil Lucky once again.\n\nTHE END!</string>
    <!-- END: user loses, leia is happy and forgives -->
    <string name="page17_4">After a tiring fight, Lucky proves to outbest you this time. He wounded you too bad to continue. As he starts barking and attacking again, you are forced to run away and hide in a tree. At that moment Snuggles jumps down from the wall between Lucky and Leia. He hisses and attacks the dog multiple times, until Lucky gives up and runs away crying. You climb down the tree.\n\nSnuggles: \"You failed to protect your kingdom AND your lady! I think it\'s time for a new king. I hereby claim this kingdom my own!\" He then turns to Leia. \"Will you rule by my side, princess?\" And bows.\nLeia hisses at him, and pushes him away. \"No! Now go away!\"\nSnuggles flattens his ears and then walks of as the new proud king. Although you lost your kingdom to Snuggles, you still have your princess at your side. Maybe one day you will have the chance to become king again.\n\nTHE END!</string>
    <!-- END: user loses, leia is angry and doesn't forgive -->
    <string name="page17_5">After a tiring fight, Lucky proves to outbest you this time. He wounded you too bad to continue. As he starts barking and attacking again, you are forced to run away and hide in a tree. At that moment Snuggles jumps down from the wall between Lucky and Leia. He hisses and attacks the dog multiple times, until Lucky gives up and runs away crying. You climb down the tree.\n\nSnuggles: \"You failed to protect your kingdom AND your lady! I think it\'s time for a new king. I hereby claim this kingdom my own!\" He then turns to Leia. \"Will you rule by my side, princess?\" And bows.\nLeia looks at you in anger. You failed to make up with her earlier today and now failed to save her from Lucky. Without saying a word she gets up and stands beside Snuggles. He gives her a headbut and together they walk away.\nToday might have been the worst day in your life. You lost your girlfriend AND your kingdom! You can only hope to fight for them both another day.\n\nTHE END!</string>
    <!-- END: user ties, leia is happy and forgives -->
    <string name="page17_6">You and Lucky fight for what seems to be hours. You both attempt a frontal attack and hit each other head to head.... and both faint.\n\nYou wake up after... minutes? Hours? Lucky is gone, but Leia is still there.\nLeia: \"Are you alright?\"\nYou: \"I don\'t know. Where is Lucky? Did I save the kingdom?\"\nLeia: \"I\'m not sure. I just waited and then Lucky woke up. Snuggles jumped down from his cowardly position on the wall and chased him away.\"\nYou: \"So Lucky could be anywhere. And Snuggles is after my throne. I have to find them...\"\nLeia: \"No, you\'re not! You have to go home and rest. You\'ll have to settle this another time.\"\n\nYou agree and together you walk home. Though the kingdom and your throne might not be save, at least Leia is happy you saved her.\n\nTHE END!</string>
    <!-- END: user ties, leia is angry and doesn't forgive -->
    <string name="page17_7">You and Lucky fight for what seems to be hours (or minutes). You both attempt a frontal attack and hit each other head to head.... and both faint.\n\nYou wake up after... minutes? Hours? Lucky is gone and Leia as well, but Snuggles is still there.\nYou: \"Where is she, you coward?!\"\nSnuggles: \"Now, now! I brought her home safe. After I defeated Lucky of course. He woke up after a few seconds and I chased him of. I don\'t think Leia is all to happy with you. I mean, you can\'t protect your kingdom and you can\'t protect her. So from now on, there\'s a new king in town. ME! So you stay away from her!\"\nAs he walks of you yell after him: \"This is not the end, Snuggles!\"\n\nHe ignores you. Today has probably been one of the worst days in your life. You lost your girlfriend AND your kingdom! You can only hope to fight for them both another day.\n\nTHE END!</string>

    <!-- Link to Simon's Cat -->
    <string name="link">\n\n\nStory: Linda de Haan\nPictures: Simon\'s Cat (https://www.youtube.com/user/simonscat)</string>
</resources>
